<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Showcase Template</title><link>https://ctatis1.github.io/showcase/docs/Exercises/</link><description>Recent content on Showcase Template</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://ctatis1.github.io/showcase/docs/Exercises/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title/><link>https://ctatis1.github.io/showcase/docs/Exercises/ColorModels/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ctatis1.github.io/showcase/docs/Exercises/ColorModels/</guid><description>Exercise Color Models # Exercise 1
Research other color models such as HSL, HSB, XYZ. Background Information # What is a colour model? # Computers understand binary language i.e. 0s and 1s. Colours are also 0s and 1s inside a computer. But while designing anything digital you do not tell the computer that hey, I want to use 01011101 colour. Obviously, we do not use the binary code. Here we use a colour model to specify a colour in terms of some parameters which in turn will send the 0’s and 1’s to the display and tell it what colour has to be shown for each desired pixel.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://ctatis1.github.io/showcase/docs/Exercises/TerrainVisualizationApp/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ctatis1.github.io/showcase/docs/Exercises/TerrainVisualizationApp/</guid><description>Exercise Color Models # Exercise 2
Develop a terrain visualization application. Check out the 3D terrain generation with Perlin noise coding train tutorial. Background Information # What is Perlin Noise? # Perlin noise is a method of generating sets of random structured numbers. While a normal random number generator will produce outputs that are completely independent from each other — excellent if you’re trying to generate a password or shuffle a deck, there are lots of instances where you want some coherence in the randomness.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://ctatis1.github.io/showcase/docs/Exercises/VisualMasking/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ctatis1.github.io/showcase/docs/Exercises/VisualMasking/</guid><description>Exercise Moiré Patterns and Kinegrams # Exercise 3
Implement a kinegram and some moiré patterns which are close related visual phenomena to masking. Moiré Pattern # &amp;ldquo;‘ Moiré ’ is a French word meaning a silk fabric that has been subjected to heat and pressure rollers after weaving to give it a rippled appearance.
The “Moiré Pattern” is an interference pattern produced by placing the similar templates , slightly offset by spacing or angle.</description></item></channel></rss>